Hi. I'm Max.
I'm a research engineer at Tessl
where I work on building a platform for evaluating coding agents.
What it means in practice is that we want to measure in a reliable way
how agent performs in real code bases, why it fails,
where it fails, and what can we do in order to fix the problems?
As agents become a part of the everyday developer life cycle, knowing
how to evaluate agents in your code base becomes a core skill for any engineer.
This March, at AI Native Dev Meetup in London, we'll talk about
how to build such platforms from scratch, how
they work and what are the real challenges in designing them.
Join us for a practical session where we will break down the key
components of building an evaluation platform, and also explore how we build
such a universal platform here at Tessl, where we allow you to evaluate
any agent with any code base, with any context in your environment.